Register of the Herbert Hoover subject collection, 1895-2006
Hoover Institution Archives
- PRESIDENTIAL FILE, 1920-1971 (Box 17-91)
  - Agriculture.
    - Extension service, Hawaii and Puerto Rico, 1929-1932.
    - Forest Service. (Box 18)
      - 1929-1930.
      - 1931-1932.
    - Miscellany.
      - Correspondence., 1930-1932.
      - Memoranda., 1931-1933.
    - Public roads, 1930-1932.
    - Seed loans, 1932-1933.
    - "Summary of Some of the New Policies, Functions, Reorganizations, and Accomplishments of the Department of Agriculture, 1930-1933," Typescript.
      - Part I.
      - Part II.
    - Weather Bureau, 1929.
  - Alien Property Custodian.
    - March - April 1929.
    - May 1929.
    - June - July 1929. (Box 19)
    - August - October 1929.
    - November - December 1929.
    - January - April 1930.
    - May - June 1930.
    - July - December 1930.
    - January - June 1931.
    - July 1931 - February 1933.
  - American Battle Monuments Commission, 1929-1931.
  - American Child Health Association, 1929-1931.
  - American Engineering Council, 1929-1933.
  - American Federation of Labor, 1929-1933.
  - American flag, 1929-1933.
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1929-1931.
  - American Green Cross, 1931.
  - American Legion.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1931-1933.
  - American National Red Cross. (Box 20)
    - 1929.
    - 1930.
    - January 1931.
    - February 1931.
    - March - December 1931.
    - 1932.
  - American Philosophical Society, 1929.
  - American Relief Administration, appropriation of $100,000,000, 1920-1930.
  - Amnesty, 1929-1932.
  - Antitrust laws, 1929-1932.
  - Appointments, n.d.
  - Appropriations, 1931-1933.
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge Commission.
    - 1929.
    - 1930.
    - 1931.
  - Armes Automatiques Lewis (Lewis Gun Co.), 1930-1931. (Box 21)
  - Armistice Day.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1930-1931.
  - Armes Automatiques Lewis (Lewis Gun Co.), 1930-1931.
  - Arms and munitions of war to Brazil, proclamation, October 22, 1930.
  - Army bases, 1929-1932.
  - Army Day, 1929-1932.
  - Artists.
    - General, 1929-1932.
    - Bronze bust of Hoover and portraits, 1929-1930.
  - Associated Press, 1932.
  - Athletics, New Recreation Conference, 1929-1932.
  - Aviation, 1930-1932.
  - Baker, George Barr.
    - Correspondence.
    - Speeches.
  - Banking crisis, 1931-1939.
  - Better Homes.
    - General.
      - 1929.
      - 1930.
      - 1931.
      - 1932-1933.
    - White House Conference on Home Building and Home Ownership.
      - 1930.
      - 1931.
      - 1932.
  - Bible, American Bible Society, 1929-1932.
  - Bills, 71st Congress, First Session, 1929.
  - Bills, 71st Congress, Second Session. (Box 22)
    - 1929 - March 1930.
    - April - May 1930.
    - June 1930.
    - July 1930.
  - Bills, 71st Congress, Third Session.
    - 1930.
    - 1931.
  - Bills, 72nd Congress, First Session.
    - January - April 1932.
    - May - July 1932.
  - Bills, 72nd Congress, Second Session, 1933. (Box 23)
  - Blind, the, 1931.
  - Bonaventure, Edmond C., 1945.
  - Bonus March.
    - General, 1931-1960.
    - The Bonus Expeditionary Forces News, 1932.
    - Hurley, Patrick, "Patrick J. Hurley Discloses the Facts about the Bonus March," McCall's, Printed copy, related testimony by John T. Pace, and related correspondence., November 1949.
    - MacArthur, Douglas, 1932-1964.
    - Newspaper clippings, 1936-1940.
    - Press releases and public statements, 1932.
    - Public opinion.
      - Re veterans' bonus legislation.
        - Approval of Administration policy.
          - January - February 1931.
          - March - August 1931. (Box 24)
          - 1932-1933.
        - Disapproval of Administration policy.
          - 1930-1931.
          - 1932.
      - Re Bonus Army.
        - July 1932.
        - August 1932.
        - September 1932.
        - Washington Trade Board, August - September 1932.
    - Reports and memoranda, 1932.
  - Boy Scouts, 1929-1932.
  - British and French economic crisis, 1932. (Box 25)
  - Building and housing, 1931.
  - Buildings, public, 1930-1931.
  - Bureau of the Budget.
    - General.
      - 1929.
      - February - May 1930.
      - July 1930.
      - July 30, 1930.
      - September - December 1930.
      - 1931-1932.
      - 1933.
    - Authorization of Navy Department and Post Office, 1932.
  - Business.
    - 1929.
    - 1930.
    - 1931-1932.
  - Cabinet. (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, 1929-1931.
    - Memoranda and printed matter, 1929.
  - California Water and Bridges Commission.
    - 1929.
    - 1930-1933.
  - California water conservation, 1922-1932.
  - Campaign of in California., 1932
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1929.
  - Century of Progress Exposition, Chicago, 1929-1933.
  - Chamber of Commerce of the U.S.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1931.
    - 1932-1933.
  - Chicago, sanitary district, 1930.
  - Children, 1929-1932.
  - Child health and protection.
    - General, 1931.
    - White House Conference of Child Health and Protection, 1929-1932.
  - Christmas, 1929-1931. (Box 27)
  - Chronology of the presidential period, n.d.
  - Churches, 1929.
  - Citizens' Military Training Camps, 1929-1931.
  - Citizenship, 1930.
  - Civil Service Commission.
    - 1929.
    - 1930.
    - 1931.
    - 1932-1933.
  - Civil Service Retirement, 1929-1932.
  - Coal mining industry.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1931-1933. (Box 28)
  - Coffee, 1932.
  - Colorado River and Hoover Dam, 1929-1933.
  - Columbus Day, 1930-1932.
  - Commerce Department.
    - General.
      - "The Function of the Commerce Department," Typescript memoranda and related correspondence., 1931.
      - 1929.
      - 1930.
      - 1931.
      - 1932.
    - Census Bureau, 1929-1933. (Box 29)
    - Coast and Geodetic Survey, 1929-1931.
    - Endorsements, 1932.
    - Fisheries, 1929-1932.
    - Foreign and domestic commerce, 1929-1932.
    - Foreign tariff, 1931.
    - Lighthouses, mines, miscellaneous, and navigation, 1929-1930.
    - Patent Office, public construction, and standards, 1929-1931.
  - Commissions, 1931-1933.
  - Community service and Community Chest, 1929-1932.
  - Comptroller General, 1930-1931.
  - Confederate matters, 1929.
  - Congress of the U.S.
    - 1929-1931.
    - 1932.
  - Conservation, 1929-1931.
  - Construction, 1929-1930.
  - Copyrights, 1931-1932. (Box 30)
  - Cost of Living, 1929-1930.
  - Cotton.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1932.
    - 1933.
  - Covered Wagon Centennial, 1930.
  - Crime, kidnapping, 1931-1932.
  - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1929-1931.
  - Depression, 1931-1933.
  - Disabled American Veterans of the World War, 1929-1931.
  - District of Columbia Commissioners.
    - General.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1931.
    - 1932.
  - Drought.
    - 1930.
    - 1931. (Box 31)
    - 1932.
  - Easter, 1929-1930.
  - Economics, 1929-1932.
  - Economy.
    - 1929-1931.
    - 1932.
    - 1933.
  - Education.
    - March 1929
    - April - May 1929.
    - June - December 1929.
    - 1930-1933.
  - Eight-hour law, 1931-1932. (Box 32)
  - Elks, Benevolent and Protective Order of, 1929-1930.
  - Engineering, 1930.
  - Expositions, 1930-1932.
  - Executive orders, miscellaneous, 1929-1932.
  - Farm matters, 1929-1933.
    - General.
      - 1929.
      - 1930-1932.
      - 1933.
    - Cattle and livestock.
    - Cooperative marketing.
    - Dairying, eggs, and poultry.
    - Export debenture bill.
    - Federal Farm Board.
      - 1929.
      - 1930. (Box 33)
      - 1931.
      - 1932.
  - Farm relief, 1929-1932.
  - Father's Day, father and son movement, 1929-1931.
  - Federal Board for Vocational Education, 1930.
  - Federal Employment Stabilization Board, 1931-1932.
  - Federal Home Loan Board.
    - General, 1931-1932.
    - Legislation, 1932.
  - Federal Power Commission.
    - General.
      - 1929-1931.
      - 1932-1933.
    - "Our Water Rights," by A. Kannenberg, Mimeographed copy., 1928.
  - Federal Radio Commission. (Box 34)
    - General.
      - 1929.
      - January - August 1930.
      - September - December 1930.
      - January 1931.
      - February - April 1931.
      - May 1931.
      - June - September 1931.
      - November - December 1931.
      - January - March 1932.
      - April 1932 - March 1933.
    - Committee to Investigate Duplication of Government Communications Facilities.
    - Interdepartmental Radio Advisory Committee.
    - Reports, miscellaneous.
  - Federal Reserve Board.
    - General.
      - 1929-1930.
      - 1931-1932.
    - Glass banking bill, 1932.
  - Federal Specifications Board, 1929. (Box 35)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1930-1932.
  - Finance.
    - General.
      - 1929-1930.
      - 1931.
      - 1932-1933.
    - Banking and bankruptcy.
      - 1929-1931.
      - 1932.
      - 1933.
    - Gold and silver.
      - 1929-1930.
      - 1931.
      - 1932.
      - 1933.
    - National Credit Corporation.
      - 1931.
      - 1932.
    - New York Stock Market Exchange.
      - General.
        - 1929-1930.
        - 1931-1932.
      - Grain and cotton, 1931-1932.
      - Short selling practices, 1929-1931.
  - Fire and fire prevention, 1929-1932. (Box 36)
  - Fishing and fisheries, 1929-1930.
  - Flax seed, 1930-1931.
  - Flood controls.
    - 1929.
    - 1930.
    - 1931-1932.
  - Football, 1929-1931.
  - Foreign policy, 1930-1933.
  - Forests, 1929-1932.
  - Franking privilege, 1932.
  - Freight rules, 1929-1930.
  - Frigate Constitution, 1930-1931.
  - Fur industry, 1929.
  - Gaiger, Philipp, 1931.
  - Game protection. (Box 37)
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1931.
    - 1932.
  - Girl Scouts, 1929-1930.
  - Gold Star Mothers, 1930-1932.
  - Government contracts, 1932.
  - Government departments.
    - 1929.
    - 1930.
    - 1931.
    - 1932.
    - 1933.
  - Government employees, 1929-1933. (Box 38)
  - Government ownership, 1930-1932.
  - Government Printing Office, 1924-1933.
  - Governors of the states, 1929-1932.
  - Grain.
    - 1929.
    - 1930.
    - January - June 1931.
    - July - December 1931.
    - 1932.
  - Greek letter fraternities, 1929.
  - Health, 1929-1931.
  - Helium, 1929-1932.
  - Highways, 1929-1931.
  - Hoarding. (Box 39)
    - February 3-8, 1932.
    - February 10 - March 9, 1932.
    - March 10 - December 31, 1932.
  - Holidays, 1929-1931.
  - Home buildings, 1931.
  - Hoover's performance as president. (See also EDITORIAL ANALYSES SERIES, boxes 296-312).
    - 1930.
      - Analysis of reports.
      - First year.
      - Topical analysis.
    - 1931. (Box 40)
      - American Legion speech, Detroit.
      - Annual message to Congress.
      - Moratorium on German debts.
      - Unemployment Conference.
    - 1932.
      - Acceptance speech.
      - Address to Welfare Conference.
      - Annual message.
      - Antihoarding appeal.
      - Antihoarding campaign.
      - Appointments.
        - A - L.
        - M - Z.
      - Budget cut proposal.
        - General.
        - Sales tax outlook.
      - Budget message.
      - Consolidation of Federal Bureaus proposal.
      - Des Moines speech.
      - Detroit speech.
      - Disarmament proposal.
      - Election result.
      - Foreign debt statement.
      - Letter to Borah on war debt.
      - Political issues. (Box 41)
      - Special message on war debts.
      - Tax increase proposals, 1932.
        - December 29, 1931 - February 15, 1932.
        - February 16 - March 15.
        - March 16 - March 31.
        - April 1 - April 14.
        - April 15 - June 2.
      - Third year.
      - Veto of Wagner-Garner Relief Bill.
      - Washington's Birthday address.
    - Special message on budget., 1933.
  - Humane organizations, 1929-1930.
  - Immigration.
    - Correspondence, 1929-1932.
    - Speeches, 1930-1932.
  - Inauguration of Herbert Hoover, March 4, 1929. (Box 42)
    - General, 1929.
    - Inaugural train from Palo Alto.
    - Invitations and programs.
  - Independence Day, 1929-1931.
  - Independent Order of Odd Fellows, 1929-1932.
  - Indians, 1929-1931. (Box 43)
  - Industrial mobilization, 1930.
  - Inland waterways, 1929-1932.
  - Interdepartmental Pay Board, 1929-1932.
  - Interior Department.
    - General.
      - 1929.
      - 1930.
      - 1931.
      - 1932.
    - Accomplishments, 1933.
    - Alaska railroad, 1930-1932.
    - Appropriations, 1932-1933.
    - Education Bureau, 1929-1930.
    - General Land Office, 1933.
    - Geological Survey, 1929.
    - Howard University, 1932.
    - Indian Office.
      - 1929-1931.
      - 1932-1933.
  - National Park Service, 1929-1932. (Box 44)
    - Public lands, executive orders withdrawing.
      - 1929.
      - January - June 1930.
      - July - August 1930.
      - September - December 1930.
      - January - April 1931.
      - May - August 1931.
      - September - December 1931.
      - January - July 1932. (Box 45)
      - August - December 1932.
      - 1933.
    - Reclamation Service, 1929-1931.
    - Virgin Islands.
      - 1931.
      - 1932-1933.
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1929-1932.
  - Irrigation, 1929-1932.
  - Island possessions, 1930.
  - Izaak Walton League of America, 1929-1932.
  - Justice Department. (Box 46)
    - General.
      - 1929.
      - 1930.
      - 1931-1933.
    - Bureau of Investigation, 1929-1932.
    - Bureau of Prohibition, 1930-1932.
    - Endorsements, 1929-1932.
    - Judiciary.
      - Circuit Judges, 1929-1932.
      - Court of Claims, 1929-1931.
      - Customs Court, 1929-1932.
    - National Training School for Boys, 1929-1932.
    - Parole Board, 1930.
  - Kellogg-Briand Treaty, anniversary statement, 1929.
  - Kiwanis Club, 1929-1932.
  - Knights of Columbus, 1929-1932.
  - Labor Department. (Box 47)
    - General.
      - 1929-1931.
      - 1932-1933.
    - Children's Bureau, 1929-1932.
    - Employment Service, 1930-1931.
    - Immigration Bureau, 1929-1933.
    - Industrial Housing and Transportation Bureau, 1929-1930.
    - Labor Day, 1929-1932.
    - Labor Statistics Bureau, 1929-1933.
    - Union shop, 1929-1932.
    - Women's Bureau, 1929.
  - Law enforcement, 1929-1930.
  - Law reform, 1929-1932.
  - League of Nations, n.d.
  - Library of Congress, 1929-1930.
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1929-1932.
  - Liquor, n.d.
  - Maps, 1929-1931.
  - Masonic matters, 1929-1932.
  - Maternity legislation, 1929-1932. (Box 48)
  - Medal of Honor, 1930-1932.
  - Medals.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1931-1932.
  - Merchant Marines.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1931-1933.
  - Mergers, 1929-1931.
  - Messages and communications to Congress, 1929-1932.
  - Military Order of the World War, 1929-1932.
  - Military reservations, 1929-1932.
  - Mines and mining, 1929-1931.
  - Miscellaneous.
  - Missouri River Commission, 1929-1932. (Box 49)
  - Monuments, 1929-1932.
  - Moratorium on war debts, 1929-1931.
  - Mother's Day, 1929-1932.
  - Motion pictures, 1929-1932.
  - Motor vehicles, 1929-1932.
  - Mount Rushmore National Memorial Commission, 1929-1932.
  - Mount Vernon Memorial Highway, 1932.
  - Muscle Shoals.
    - 1929-1930.
    - February 1931.
    - March 1931.
    - June - December 1931.
  - Music, 1929-1931. (Box 50)
  - National Archives, 1930-1932.
  - National Capital Park and Planning Commission, 1929-1932.
  - National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement.
    - General, 1929-1930.
    - Reports, 1929-1931.
    - Wickersham Report, comments.
      - A - D.
      - E - G.
      - H - K. (Box 51)
      - L - R.
      - S - Z.
  - National Committee on Wood Utilization, 1929-1933.
  - National Conference on Business and Industrial Committees, 1932.
  - National Conference on City Planning, 1929-1930.
  - National Conference on Street and Highway Safety, 1930.
  - National Defense, 1929-1932.
  - National Economy League, 1932.
  - National Institute of Health, 1930-1931.
  - National Electric Light Association, 1929-1930.
  - National Memorial Association, 1929-1931.
  - National Recreation Association, 1931.
  - National Timber Conservation Board, 1930-1932.
  - Naval Treaties, 1929-1931.
  - Navy.
    - General.
      - 1928.
      - 1929.
      - 1930.
      - January - July 1931. (Box 52)
      - August - December 1931.
      - 1932.
    - Aeronautics Bureau and Assistant Secretary of the Navy for Aeronautics, 1931-1932.
    - Battle efficiency pennant, 1929-1930.
    - General Board of Navy, 1926-1931.
    - Guam, 1929-1931.
    - Marine Band, 1929-1932.
    - Marine Corps, 1929-1932.
    - Naval Academy applicants, 1929-1932.
    - Naval Academy, Board of Visitors, 1929-1933.
    - Naval Conference at Camp Rapidan, 1931.
    - Naval Reserve, 1932.
    - Navigation Bureau, 1932.
    - Navy Band, 1930-1932.
    - Navy economy and reductions, 1929-1931.
    - Navy line personnel bill, 1931.
    - Navy Yard, 1929-1932.
    - Samoa, 1929-1931. (Box 53)
    - Surgeon General of the Navy, 1932-1933.
    - Virgin Islands.
      - 1929-1930.
      - 1931.
  - Newspapers, 1929-1932.
  - Oil matters.
    - General, 1929-1932.
    - Colorado Springs Petroleum Conference, 1929.
    - Federal Oil Conservation Board, 1929.
  - Olympic Games, 1929-1932.
  - Oratorical contests, 1929-1932.
  - Packers, packing industry, 1930-1932.
  - Pardons, 1929.
  - Parents-Teachers Association, 1929-1931.
  - Patents, 1930-1932.
  - Pens used by the President.
    - 1929-1930.
    - 1931-1933.
  - Pensions, 1929-1931.
  - Perry's Victory Memorial Commission, 1929-1931.
  - Personnel files, arranged according to original office file system., 1929-1932 (Box 54)
    - Appointments to various government positions, arranged alphabetically by name of applicant.
    - List of endorsements by Senators and Representatives, arranged alphabetically by name of sponsor.
      - A - J.
      - K - Z. (Box 55)
    - State Department, positions of ambassador and minister, applicants arranged alphabetically by name of country.
    - Applicants to various posts in the Departments of War, Justice, Commerce, and Interior. Arranged by state of applicant and name of position or bureau. (Box 56)
    - Applicants for positions in the Department of Interior, Justice, Labor, Navy, Post Office, and State, arranged by the title of the position. (Box 57)
    - Applicants for positions in the Departments of the Treasury, Justice, Labor and various commissions, arranged by the state of the applicant. (Box 58)
      - Arkansas - Minnesota.
      - Mississippi - Puerto Rico. (Box 59)
      - Rhode Island - Wyoming. (Box 60)
    - Applicants for miscellaneous positions arranged by name of the commission or position.
      - Alien Property Custodian - Public Printer.
      - Radio Commission - Veterans' Bureau. (Box 61)
    - Applicants for unspecified positions, arranged by name and category.
    - White House employees, arranged by name.
    - Department of Agriculture, appointments arranged by bureau.
    - Applicants for various positions, arranged by commission or title. (Box 62)
      - Public Utilities, Civil Service, Federal Power, National Memorial Association, Radio Commission, Interstate Commerce, Tariff Commission, U.S. Board of Mediation, U.S. Compensation, U.S. Shipping Board, Governor of Hawaii, Justice, Chief Justice of the Supreme Court, Attorney General.
      - U.S. Customs Court, Court of Claims, Associate Justice, Circuit Judge for the Third, Fourth, Fifth and Ninth Circuits, Director of Prohibition, Solicitor General, District Judges for Alabama, Alaska, California, and the District of Columbia. (Box 63)
    - Appointments to various positions, arranged by bureau.
      - Drought Commission - Federal Trade Commission.
      - Fine Arts Commission - Washington Memorial Commission. (Box 64)
    - State Department, appointments, arranged by bureau or title. (Box 65)
    - Appointments to various positions, arranged by state of applicant. (Box 66)
    - Department of the Interior, appointments, arranged by bureau.
    - Justice Department, appointments, arranged by bureau.
    - Justice, Judiciary, appointments, arranged by court.
    - Justice, Judiciary, appointments, arranged by state. (Box 67)
    - Treasury Department, appointments, arranged by bureau.
    - War Department, appointments, arranged by bureau. (Box 68)
    - Appointments to various bureaus and commissions.
    - Commerce Department, appointments, arranged by bureau.
    - Justice Department, appointments, arranged by state of applicant.
      - Florida - Pennsylvania.
      - Philippine Islands - Wyoming. (Box 69)
    - Department of Labor, appointments, arranged by bureau.
    - Navy, appointments, arranged by bureau.
    - Post Office, appointments, arranged by name of employee.
    - Justice and Treasury Departments, applications, arranged by state.
      - Florida - Minnesota.
      - Mississippi - Texas. (Box 70)
    - Secretary of Labor, applicants, arranged by name.
    - Navy, applicants, arranged by name.
    - War Department, applicants, arranged by name.
    - State Department, applicants, arranged by name.
    - Ambassadors and ministers, applicants, arranged by country.
    - Treasury Department, applicants, arranged by bureau. (Box 71)
    - War Department, applicants, arranged by name.
    - Justice Department, applicants, arranged by district.
    - Treasury Department, applicants, arranged by bureau.
    - Commerce Department, appointments, arranged by name. (Box 72)
    - Department of Agriculture, applicants, arranged by name.
    - Assistant Comptroller General, applicants, arranged by name.
    - Commission on Law Enforcement, applicants, arranged by name.
  - Phonograph recordings, 1929-1932. (Box 73)
  - Planning, national, 1929-1931.
  - Post Office.
    - General.
      - 1929.
      - 1930.
      - 1931.
      - 1932-1933.
    - Postal Savings Bank, 1931-1933.
    - Postmasters, 1929-1932.
    - Post Office leases, 1930.
  - Power, 1929-1931.
  - Presidency of Herbert Hoover.
    - General.
      - Activities as President, 1933.
      - Defense of the Hoover administration by E.E. Hunt, Untitled typescript memoranda with related correspondence and clippings., 1928-1932.
      - Office of the President, 1929-1931.
    - campaign, Hoover as potential presidential candidate., 1920 (Box 74)
      - American press and public opinion, 1920-1921.
      - German press reports.
    - campaign., 1928
      - Acknowledgement of letters of congratulation. Holograph draft.
      - Campaign materials.
        - General.
        - Campaign statements of Hoover, miscellaneous.
        - Political songs.
        - Republican National Committee pamphlets.
        - Republican organizations in California.
          - Pamphlets.
          - Speakers' Bulletin.
      - Correspondence between Hoover supporters.
        - General.
        - Brown, Everett S., 1924-1928.
        - Sullivan, Mark.
          - 1927.
          - 1928. (Box 75)
            - A - Q.
            - R - Z.
          - Memoranda
      - Endorsements of Hoover.
      - History of the California campaign, 1929.
      - Press releases relating to election returns.
      - Republican National Convention.
        - General.
        - Minutes of the meetings of the California delegation.
    - campaign., 1932 (Box 76)
      - Democratic Party.
        - General.
        - Democratic convention.
          - General.
          - Literature on favorite son candidates.
        - Democratic National Committee reports and literature.
        - Democratic State Central Committee, California.
        - Statement of the Democratic platform and related commentary.
      - Minor parties.
      - Prohibitionist literature.
      - Reilly's Free Press, Oakland, California. (Box 77)
      - Republican Party.
        - General.
        - Editorial comment summaries, November 1932.
        - Endorsements of Hoover.
        - National 32 Club material.
        - Political songs.
        - Republican National Committee information sheets.
        - Republican National Committee pamphlets.